Contact

abila.bogle@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/april-bogle-rn-cen-sane-247399a8 (LinkedIn) www.indeed.com/r/973b45b7400da210 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Project Coordination Cardiac Care Hospitals

Certifications

Certified Stroke Coordinator

ACLS

TNCC

BLS

Chest Pain Coordinator

April Bogle RN, CEN, SANE

Regenerative Medicine RN

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Summary

Certified Platelet Rich Plasma provider specialized in PRP injections for: rotator cuff injury, tennis elbow, arthritic knees, vaginal rejuvenation, male ED, fine lines and wrinkles, dark circles and skin discoloration. Nurse injector for dermal fillers and toxins.

Experienced, Board Certified Emergency Registered Nurse specialized in the Emergency Department with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry.

Skilled in Emergency Management, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Emergency Medicine, Emergency Medical Services (EMS), and Physician Relations.

Experience

Timeless Regerative Aesthetics Certified Platelet Rich Plasma Consultant March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months) Dickson, Tennessee

Aesthetic Nurse Injector specializes in the Platelet Rich Plasma

Nashville General Hospital Emergency Room Nurse January 2020 - Present (7 months) Greater Nashville Area, TN

Tristar Ashland City Medical Center Forensic Nurse Examiner SANE April 2019 - January 2020 (10 months) Ashland City

Forensic nurses perform duties that are much more specialized than nurses typically perform. They have a variety of roles, including evaluating and caring for victims of assault, domestic abuse, child and elder abuse, neglect, and

sexual crimes. As they treat the victim, forensic nurses collect and secure evidence.

TriStar Ashland City Emergency Department Emergency Room RN, CEN, SANE March 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 1 month) Greater Nashville Area, TN

Anesthesia Medical Group
Pre Op Nurse
November 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 5 months)
Greater Nashville Area, TN

Tristar Hendersonville Medical Center Emergency Department RN May 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 7 months) Hendersonville, Tennessee

TriStar Centennial Medical Center Emergency Department RN November 2015 - April 2016 (6 months) Greater Nashville Area

Any opinions, views, or comments are of my own and do not reflect the opinion of my employer.

NorthCrest Medical Center 5 years 4 months

Chest Pain Coordinator
April 2014 - October 2015 (1 year 7 months)
NorthCrest Medical Center

Evaluate and improve the diagnosis and treatment of patients who present with symptoms of a heart attack.

ED Charge Nurse July 2010 - August 2015 (5 years 2 months) Springfield, Tennessee

My primary job is to help hold the department together by providing guidance to less experienced nurses, making assignments and requesting additional staff if needed. I also field complaints from disgruntled patients and serve as a liaison with doctors and other hospital staff. As an ER charge nurse, I have

strong leadership skills, flexibility and the ability to remain calm and assertive even in high-pressure situations.

AeroCare Medical Transport
RN Flight Nurse
August 2009 - May 2010 (10 months)
Winslow, AZ

Fixed Wing Flight Nurse in the desert of Arizona and surrounding areas.

Air Evac Lifeteam

Base Nurse Supervisor

May 2006 - August 2009 (3 years 4 months)

Education

Western Governors University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2021)

Creighton University
EMT, Emergency Medicine · (2006 - 2006)

Columbia State Community College
Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2000 - 2002)

Tennessee Technology Center at Dickson Certificate, Nursing · (1993 - 1994)